you
Hi.
Hi, I am the pharmacist.
My name is Anubhav.
How can I help you?
My feet are driving me crazy.
Can you give me something to fix it quickly?
Yeah, sure.
But do you mind if I ask you a few questions so that I can provide you the most appropriate treatment?
Sure.
Can I first have your name, age and medical number?
My name is Naga.
Medical number is URN 23456.
And your age?
It's 50 years.
Right.
Do you mind if I just explain more about your symptoms?
Okay, there is a flaking and itchiness between the toes.
Okay.
Is there any other unusual symptoms that you are having a fever or that's a swelling of the skin area?
No.
Okay.
How long have the symptoms been present?
This is there for almost three weeks.
Three weeks?
Okay.
Have you tried anything to relieve your symptoms yet?
No.
Okay.
Perhaps you have any idea on what might have caused your symptoms?
I am not very sure but I am working in the firm so I will be wearing the boots of the lady.
Is this the first time you are experiencing such symptoms?
Do you have any medical conditions?
No.
Are you taking any medication, supplements or herbal treatment?
Do you have any allergies?
No.
Okay.
Is there any proliferation of the medication?
I will be happy if it is a cream.
Okay, sure.
Do you mind to just give me a moment to check on my resources?
Sure.
Okay, so hi sir, thanks for waiting.
It seems that you are having a tin of patties or as known as actually foods which may be caused by the foods that you are bearing because it calms your food so it creates a humid environment for the fungus to grow.
It is very common so do not worry about that.
And here's the medication for you, which is a 1% turbinaffin cream.
It is a fast relief medication which you can just apply once daily for 7 days onto the affected area.
But before you apply, please ensure that you shower before you apply onto the affected area and make sure it is dry and clean.
Okay?
So while using this medication that could be some side effects like burning or stinging sensation, it is usually more tolerated.
However, if you feel that the side effects are unbearable, you can always come back to the pharmacies for a switch of medication.
In addition to the medication, I will also suggest you to try out something that's not so occlusive.
Try something that is able to give your food circulation of air so that it doesn't create a humid environment.
and also dry the affected area using a separate towel and do not share towels with any others.
So if I do have any questions for you?
I do not have any questions.
I believe I've given you a lot of information.
Do you mind to repeat after what I've mentioned?
I understood all the information given with you.
Right, so here's the medication together with the written left nerve as a guidance.
If your symptoms got worse or you don't resolve after one week of treatment, you should visit the doctor immediately for further investigation.
I hope we get well soon.
Okay.